Kenny Becerra

Programmer/CyberSecurity Analyst





About me

Solution-driven and project oriented, I am a programmer with a passion for front-end development. My background is in computer engineering and my technical career path has centered around developing/managing tools for process improvement and automation. Checkout my github to see some of the Front-end dev projects I've worked on.



Skills

HTML/CSS

 ✓ HTML5 ✓ CSS2/CSS3 ✓ SASS/LESS ✓ Flexbox ✓ CSS Grid ✓ Responsive Design ✓ Bootstrap JAVASCRIPT				
✓ ES5	✓ ES6	✓ ES7	✓ AJAX	✓ Jquery
TOOLS				

✓ NPM✓ Webpack✓ Gulp✓ Grunt✓ Git Version Control
✓ VS Code



Work Experience

Programmer/CyberSecurity Analyst at Pacific Gas & Electric

San Francisco, CA January 2017 - Present

Developed and maintained Third-Party Security team systems and tools.

Utilized SQL, VBA scripts, and Python to enhance current system tools reporting, and metrics

Enhanced processes through automation using VBA and Python.

Managed team repositories/tools in MS Access, SharePoint, and MetricStream.

Programmer/IT Analyst at Pacific Gas & Electric

San Francisco, CA August 2015 - December 2016

Developed scripting solutions for Energy Procurement Support team Ad-hoc requests.

Developed UI functionality for Energy Procurement System tools using SQL, and VBA.

Automated administrative tasks and workflows using VBA, python and SharePoint Rest API'

Software Engineering intern at General Electric

Waukesha, WI May 2014 - August 2014

Developed scripts in Lua and Python language for software testing and data manipulation Researched integration of DDS (Data Distribution Services) for CT Scanner middleware Evaluated integration methods of DDS and updated code information/manual



Education

Bachelors of Science in Computer Engineering

Florida State University



Contact

X

kennybecerra.j@gmail.com



https://github.com/kennybecerra



www.linkedin.com/in/kennybecerra/



https://kennybecerra.github.io/